friendite.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy|Friendite.com

Friendite Is the world most popular social utility that connects love ones with friends and others who work, study and live around them. People use friendite to keep up with friends, families, business partners, events, shows, love ones, Facebook friends, twitter friends, google friends, MySpace friends and more... 

We are glad to welcome you to www.friendite.com Please read this privacy statement to ensure that we are committed to keeping secure the privacy of our members' (customers) details. 

Friendite.com is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our web sites as well as the privacy of our actual customers. 

For visitors, we've structured our web sites so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. 

For customers, once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with Friendite.com. Visitors To Our Web Site 

What information do we collect? 

When you visit our web site, our web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP's domain, the time you accessed our web site, and the pages from within our web site that you visit. 

We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a web site can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. 

Our web server does not collect your e-mail address or aggregate information on what other pages on the Web you have accessed or visited. 

How do we use this information? 

The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze web traffic and to improve the content of our web site. Cookies may be used to facilitate your customer interaction with us. For example, we may use a cookie on the landing page of products sold online which record the customer information that is required on the order form and then forward this information to our internal sales tracking database. 

We may from time to time disclose to third parties aggregate information on our web site's traffic profile. For example, Internet advertising companies may require this data to help us better target our advertisements on our web site(s) and/or other web sites. 

Note that our site provides links to products and services offered by other companies; the company's web site that you link to will be able to determine that you linked from our web site. Dating Site Builder Signed Up Members 

What information do we collect? 

When you sign up for Friendite.com, you provide us with both contact and payment information. Contact information typically includes your name, address, and phone number. Payment information typically includes your credit card number will be kept by our credit card payment gateway - Internet Secure. 

While you are a Friendite.com member, we manage information with regard to your account status, choice of services, and member logs. In addition, we may store members' electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications. 

How do we use this information? 

We use the contact information you provide us to establish our service for you. We use payment information for payment processing purposes only. We create and maintain other information such as member account status, choice of services, and member logs in the normal course of providing service. 

Friendite may share member information with selected partners/third parties, for example, to provide you with information about products which might be of interest to you or to enable you to take advantage of special partner programs.Friendite may also use member information to provide members with system information or information about new or upgraded products. 

We will not otherwise disclose member personal and account information unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of Friendite.com, our members, or others, or where Friendite.com has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure. 

Friendite.com also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that Friendite.com stores or transmits for its members. The circumstances under which Friendite.com will disclose such electronic members comm unications are when: 

It is necessary in order to provide service to the member; It is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of Friendite.com and its members; It is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that Friendite.com determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and It is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by Friendite.com and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime. 

Friendite.com disclaims any intention to censor, edit, or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by members or others. Friendite.com will, however, review, delete, or block access to communications that may harm Friendite.com, its members or third parties. The grounds on which Friendite.com may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of Friendite.com Terms of Use. 

Members may opt out of receiving newsletters and/or notices of new or upgraded products from Friendite.com by sending a request to support@friendite.com. In this request, members must identify their domain name and contact information. Please note, however, that Friendite.com reserves the right to send bulletins and other important information regarding our services at our discretion. 

**What information do we collect?**  
Since is providing you the software and support to build a website, we may require from you some information that may be considered as personally identifiable.

Please provide us with the following information about yourself: 

  * username
  * real name
  * password
  * e-mail address

Other personal information that we may possibly need: To be able to render the services you've ordered, we may need information about your website: site URL, FTP, cPanel or SSH accesses.

**Copyrights**  
All site contents copyrights are reserved by Justmestunner Ltd. and content copying and duplication are strongly prohibited.

**Acceptance of agreements**  
By reading this you agree to our Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to our terms and conditions you may not use this site. We may update our Privacy Statement from time to time so please visit this page regularly.
